pornflixer.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy

PornFlixer.com encourages its customers, users as well as visitors and others who use or visit PornFlixer to appreciate their privacy. This particular privacy notice and its details are holding very important information related to usage and disclosure of the information about user that has been collected or stored on the PornFlixer website. This notice of privacy has been provided to you in order to assist you in making the correct and reliable decision regarding the further use our website.

Please be noted that any type of content including videos and images that have been posted in the users’ direction at PornFlixer website automatically become recognized as published content and cannot be considered as personally identifiable information that is subject to this particular note about privacy terms.

Information provided by user: Be aware that you provide definite information that is being personally identifiable to PornFlixer in case when you select the participation in different types of activities on websites. For example, posting messages and uploading videos are included in the list. Your name and email address are being included in this section.

**Our Commitment to Legal-Age Usage**

Protecting children from adult content is especially important. For that reason, PornFlixer does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the PornFlixer web site from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18, or legal age according to state law. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the PornFlixer web site at any time or in any manner. If PornFlixer learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected, appropriate steps will be taken to delete this information. 

In the case of Alliance, Sale or else Bankruptcy In the case when PornFlixer is being owned by or combined with any entity from third party, we still preserve the right, in any of conditions and/or circumstances, to transfer as well as accredit the collected information from our users, which is a part of such cases as alliance, attainment, sale, as well as any other type of change in control. In cases when bankruptcy, destitution, reconstruction, receivership, as well as other assignment for the creditors’ benefit, or cases of laws’ application and impartial principles, which can affect the rights of creditors, we may not be able to monitor or control the way that your private information is being treated, used or transferred.

**Updates and Changes in Privacy Notice**

This particular privacy notice can be revised on periodic basis and users are advised to examine and check it periodically in order to stay informed in case of any changes being done. If you continue to use of the PornFlixer website, then it means that you agree to this particular privacy notice and any possible revisions of it in the future.
